Oh
Tomiko Vegas
which is no loss of the season
at a PC out never all my hopes for this
battles get me so good you guys
my dream one more
now we Chi are you know our steering
wheel can turn at low speeds there's gas
[Music]
we type through the ICO
one time I touch the screen
[Music]
let's mess your camera
most of driving is leading in traffic
like this
[Music]
I'm really a member
oh it's Evans least 20 minutes come back
alright this why did you get fire
[Music]
and we'll sweater open can save 200
bucks
[Music]
the model do
it's just getting this getting so good
and I think there's been some tuning
guns or the control oh you guys zero
point three point four they're gonna
scratch that guy
I don't know is it the model or the
control why does it feel so good I think
you'll get the bonus come on we haven't
been in the car
[Music]
yeah well I was gonna pull no I also
haven't used we change the way to model
strands or channel awesome
[Music]
and that's like that's not
it is a nice little ol boss but you know
what's really bad
oh you guys won't believe this
- I've never felt off the toilet yeah
so good
they look at a button compared to the
old one
this is driving better - thank you
this literally this is better than me
[Music]
and we gotta go to the airport I'm gonna
miss my flight already check out my tie
I got important things to go to
a rap battle rap out a rap battle some
point I know
TBD email
this track throw is going so small
should I change lanes yeah
it's driving so nicely oh I don't even
want to you know you guys this is
[Music]
quality quality we're finally at quality
you should tell them how happy there's
inertia you should hold some cash I
[Music]
don't know yeah I'll tell Michael he'll
be good motivation I'm just very happy
with your piloting yeah
probably all the space they have you
know right everyone needs a hundred if
you work at comma got one hundred square
feet of space this is all I do is video
I don't like make space look how much
space maybe make it happen
execution
what my job bro
I think it's a loss
but it's just like the waffle
Automation
good idea mom usually watch the car guys
work when their growth
got it
engage
those cards you got a think is it
engaged is it desires I know I'm on a
pedal I know it's just you guys have no
idea what's coming
- that seriously this is like the ICO is
Timothy fire but this is gonna be super
hot fire yeah yeah nook is not this not
just this is good
yes yes gonna be fire and wait'll you
guys see zero points
you don't know life
this is slightly see it drifts out
Hayate or toy export good sort
you put the torque mod back when here
for us
you might make your play
the great song
what next
today we're going to fly
I hate all I hate puns I hate corny
now I shouldn't the new wasp on you to
be better about this town
[Music]
New Jersey New Jersey's best date I Love
New Jersey
[Music]
it's gotta be Alize money method
bracelets
[Music]
tell my money forget about this
not anyone local bitcoins in Vegas get
some bitcoins I could tell
[Music]
yeah let's save on the cars go back guys
go